iraqexpoonline.com 2013-03-11

# Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the IMC Business Global Plc treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your business for inclusion in our database.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the IMC Business Global Plc network of web sites, nor does it extend to people that IMC Business Global Plc does not employ or manage.

###  Information Collection and Use

IMC Business Global Plc offers three types of site listings - Silver, Gold and Platinum. Unlike many directories that charge for site listings and collect personal information as well, IMC Business Global Plc Silver listings are free and the information we collect is primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services, and generally this information is not shared with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected, if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that the law requires such disclosure or other special cases described below.

For our Standard Free Listings, membership is required under a valid verified email address. Upon the creation of a new member account, you will be subscribed to IMC Business Global Plc monthly newsletter and updates.

Your use of IMC Business Global Plc's services constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your web site(s). In exchange, IMC Business Global Plc reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide free newsletters, to inform you of additions to the IMC Business Global Plc Network of web sites, or to send important announcements.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings.

###  Registration

Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, email e.t.c.. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). IMC Business Global Plc does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.

However, in instances where IMC Business Global Plc and a partner jointly promote the Services, IMC Business Global Plc may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, the partner may not use personal information for any other purpose.

IMC Business Global Plc may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.

###  Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. IMC Business Global Plc may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

###  Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to IMC Business Global Plc staff.

IMC Business Global Plc does not store any credit card information, as all transactions are processed by PayPal or sold through 2Checkout.com or other third party approved Credit Card processor.

###  Special Cases

It is IMC Business Global Plc policy not to use or share personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, IMC Business Global Plc may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect IMC Business Global Plc and our Members.

###  Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition of IMC Business Global Plc with another entity or multiple entities, all (or select aspects) of IMC Business Global Plc's customer information (including email addresses) may be transferred to a separate entity or entities. All IMC Business Global Plc subscribers and registered users will be notified within five business days of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of IMC Business Global Plc's assets by a third party. Subscribers and users may choose to access and modify any of their registration and subscription information at that time.

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy

IMC Business Global Plc may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.
